A Guide to the Records of the Office of Academic Affairs, 1961-1977 (bulk 1965-1976)
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- Series XI: Records and Correspondence, 1971-1974
  - Subseries L: Correspondence, Reports and Papers, A-Z, 1972-1974
    - University Services, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - UPAA - "Courses by Newspaper" Series, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Upward Bound, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - V's, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Veterans, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Veterinary Medicine (2 folders), 1974 (Box 48, Folder 16-17)
    - Vice President for Administration, 1971-1974 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Academy of Science, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Academy of Science Nominees, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - VPI&SU Industry Center, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Virginia Tech Computing Center Log, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Visiting Scholar (2 folders), 1974 (Box 48, Folder 23-24)
    - Water Resources Research Center, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Weighted Student Credit Hours, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Western Virginia Consortium, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Women, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Work Study Program, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), 1974 (Box 48, Folder 30)
- Series XII: Records and Correspondence, 1974-1975
  - Subseries A: College of Agriculture, 1974-1975
    - Agriculture Correspondence (2 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
  - Subseries B: College of Architecture, 1974-1975
    - Architecture Correspondence (3 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 3-5)
    - Architecture - Fire Control, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Subseries C: College of Arts and Sciences, 1974-1975
    - Art, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Arts and Sciences Correspondence, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Biology, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Chemistry, 1974-1978 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Computer Science, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - English, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Foreign Languages, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Geography, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Geology, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Geophysics, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - History, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Law School, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Physics, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Political Science, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Psychology - Festinger, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Subseries D: College of Business, 1974-1975
    - College of Business Correspondence (2 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 22-23)
    - Economics, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Subseries E: College of Education, 1974-1975
    - Education (6 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 25-30)
    - Administrative and Educational Services, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - Curriculum and Instruction, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Demise Report, 1975-1976 (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Health, Physical Education and Recreation, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 34-35)
    - New Faculty, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - Teacher Education and School Service Personnel Programs, Vol. 1: Basic Programs, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - Vocational and Technical Education (4 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 38, Box 50, Folder 1-3)
    - EPDA - Budget (Vocational- Technical Education), 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Subseries F: College of Engineering, 1974-1975
    - Engineering (2 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 5-6)
    - Engineering Extension, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Subseries G: College of Home Economics, 1974-1975
    - Home Economics, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Subseries H: College of Veterinary Medicine, 1974-1975
    - Veterinary Medicine - Dean Talbot (2 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 9-10)
    - Graduate School (2 folders), 1970-1975 (Box 50, Folder 11-12)
  - Subseries I: Graduate School, 1974-1975
    - Graduate School, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Graduate School Problems, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Subseries J: Extension, 1974-1975
    - Extension, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Subseries K: Commissions, 1974-1975
    - Commission on Graduate Studies and Research, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Commission on Student Affairs (2 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 17-18)
    - Commission on Undergraduate Studies (2 folders), 1975 (Box 50, Folder 19-20)
  - Subseries L: Correspondence, Reports and Papers, A-Z, 1974-1975
    - Academic Appeals Committee, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Academic Drops and Academic Information, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Academy of Teaching Excellence (4 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 23-26)
    - University Accounting, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Accreditation, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Ad Hoc Grievance Committee (2 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 29-30)
    - Adjunct Approvals, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Administrative Conference, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - Admissions, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - Advisory Committee - 1202 Commission, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Alumni, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Anaerobe Laboratory Manual, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Animal Care Laboratory, 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Army - Project Ahead, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Athletic Association - Includes Title IX, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Awards - Faculty, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Awards - Students, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Board of Visitors, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Budget Director, Business Manager, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Building Committee, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Career Advising, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Catalog Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Catalog Copy, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Center for Continuing Education, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Center for Environmental Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Center for Study of Public Choice, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Center for Systematics Collections, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Central Virginia Consortium, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Commencement Committee, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Committee on Employee Benefits, 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Committee on Faculty Affairs, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Committee on Grade Escalation, 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Committee on International Programs (2 folders), 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 26-27)
    - Communications Services, 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Community College - Radio Consortium (VPTC), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Computer Allocations - Computer Center, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education in Northern Virginia (3 folders), 1972-1975 (Box 51, Folder 31-33)
    - Consulting Activities Report, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Co-op, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Copying Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - Corp of Cadets, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - Dr. John Costain - Professor of Geophysics, 1972, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - Council of Deans, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Courses by Newspaper, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Credit Union, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - Dean's Memos (2 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 42-43)
    - An Evaluation of Management Training at the Naval Weapons Laboratory, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - An Evaluation of Technical Training for Professionals at the Dahlgren Laboratory, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Executive Vice President, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Leaves, A-K, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Leaves, L-Z, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Final Exam Policy, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - FM Radio Stations - Telecommunications, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - General Counsel, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - General Counsel - Class Action Suits, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Governor's Day, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Grades, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - GTA - Workload Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Health Services Film Program (Telecommunications), 1975 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - HEAR Programming Committee (VPTC and SCHEV), 1975 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Honors Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Honors Program, 1973-1975 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Industry Center, 1973-1975 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Information Exchange Procedures Meeting (2 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 18-19)
    - Information Services, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - International Programs (2 folders), 1975 (Box 52, Folder 21-22)
    - Dr. Amina Kazem, 1975-1976 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - A.H. Krebs - Personal, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Learning Resources Center (LRC) (2 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 26-27)
    - Learning Resources Center - Expenditures, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Learning Resources Center - Microwave Link, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Legislature, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Letters to/from Students and Parents, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - Library (3 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 32-34)
    - Library - Circulation System, 1973-1975 (Box 52, Folder 35)
    - Library Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 52, Folder 36)
    - Meetings with Selected Students, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 39)
    - Metric System, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 40)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (NASULGC), 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - NASULGC Curricular (2 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 2-3)
    - National Career Guidance, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education (NCATE) (2 folders), 1975-1976 (Box 53, Folder 5-6)
    - National Medal of Science Award, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - National Occupational Competency Testing Institute, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Navy Reserve Officer Training Corps, 1972, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Non-Traditional Degree (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Ron Nurse - History, 1973-1976 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Occupational Health and Safety, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Office Management, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Office of Institutional Research, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Other Colleges (2 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 15-16)
    - Overload Report, 1973-1975 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Patent Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Pentagon Programs (2 folders), 1973-1975 (Box 53, Folder 19-20)
    - Performance Arts and Communications (2 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 21-22)
    - Personnel, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Physics - George B. Collins, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Prison Project, Telecommunications, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Promotions, 1973-1975 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Purchasing, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Radiation Safety Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Reconciliation Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Reeves, J.B. - Topic Seminar, 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Registrar, 1973-1975 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Registration, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Research Division - Correspondence (2 folders), 1974 (Box 53, Folder 34-35)
    - Research Equipment Inventory, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Residential College Committee, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - Reston, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - Reston - Computer Needs, 1973-1975 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - Reston - Library, 1973-1975 (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - Reston - Space, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - Retirement, 1973-1975 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Reynolds Homestead Research Center (AGRIC), 1973-1975 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - ROTC, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - ROTC Courses for Veterans, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Scholarships, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - SEA - Grant, 1972-1975 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Senior Citizens, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Society of Cincinnati, 1973-1974 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Southern Regional Education Board (SREB), 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Special Academic Programs (2 folders), 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 10-11)
    - Sporn Award, 1968, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Student Advisory Committee, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Student Problems, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Study Abroad, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Teaching Excellence, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Teaching- Learning Grants, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Telecommunications, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Telecommunications Resources Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Tenure Data, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Timetable, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Town of Blacksburg, 1973-1976 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Transfer Articulation Conference, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Transfer Student, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Travel, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - TV Program Development Proposals, Forms, and Budgets, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - United Nations University, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - University Awards Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - University Development, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Upper Iowa University - Extension Program, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Upward Bound Program, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Veterans, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - VPTC Contract and Monthly Reports - Forms, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 33-34)
    - Visiting Scholar Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - WBRA - Microwave Link, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - Women's Studies Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 37)
- Series XIII: Correspondence, Reports, and Papers, 1975-1976
  - Commission on Faculty Affairs: Professor Nominations, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 38)
  - Cheatham Hall Dedication, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - Raymond E. Dessy, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 40)
  - William A. Duerr, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 41)
  - Education - Dabney S. Lancaster, Community College, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - R.W. Engel, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 43)
  - Extension, 1976-1977 (Box 54, Folder 44)
  - Professor Olivio C. Ferrari - Distinguished Professor Nomination, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 45)
  - Grathwol - History, 1972-1976 (Box 54, Folder 46)
  - Lillian Virginia Holdeman, Professor of Microbiology, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 47)
  - Bruce C. Parker, Distinguished Professor Nomination, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Paul B. Siegel, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Professor William E. Skelton, Distinguished Professor Nomination, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Alan Walter Steiss, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - University Professors, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Series XIV: Proposed Degree Programs, 1970-1974
  - Proposal for Baccalaureate Degree in Religious Studies, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Proposal for a Religion Option in Philosophy Degree, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Performing Arts and Communications Curriculum - Bachelor of Arts in Communication, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Computer Science and Applications - Master of Science, 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Doctor of Philosophy in Computer Science and Applications (2 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 55, Folder 10-11)
  - Bachelor of Science, Master of Science and Doctor of Philosophy with a Major in Food Science and Technology, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Master of Arts and Doctor of Education (3 folders), 1970 (Box 55, Folder 13-15)
  - Proposal for Doctoral Degree in Education, Part I, 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Proposal for Doctor of Education Degree, Part II (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 17-18)
  - Proposal to Consolidate Bachelor's Programs in Education, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Undergraduate Degree Program in Education, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Master of Arts in Education: A Basic Program with Seven Options, 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Master of Arts in Education Proposal - Special Learning Disabilities, 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Special Learning Disabilities, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Proposal for Professional Development in the Areas of Specific Learning Disabilities and the Emotionally Disturbed, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Five-Year Program Plan, Division of Vocational-Technical Education, 1972-1976 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Request to Recognize Four Program Options under Virginia Tech Master of Education Degree Authorization of 1951, 1972-1976 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Proposal for Doctor of Philosophy, Option in Educational Research and Evaluation, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - College of Education - Post Masters Advising Manual, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Graduate Fellowship Program for Leadership Development in Vocational and Technical Education (2 folders), 1975 (Box 55, Folder 29-30)
  - Doctor of Philosophy - Major in Business, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Doctor of Philosophy - Major in Business Volume II, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Proposal for the Creation of a New Curriculum in the College of Engineering, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Program - Electrical Engineering Technology, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Doctor of Philosophy in English, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Doctor of Philosophy with a Major in Psychology (2 folders) (Box 56, Folder 6-7)
  - Doctor of Philosophy - Major in Sociology (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - PhD in Sociology - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Proposed New Degree Program - Master of Urban Affairs (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - PhD in Water Technology - Name Change, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Series XV: Task Force on Innovation, 1972-1974
  - Task Force Innovation in Instruction, 1972-01-1972-02 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Task Force for Innovation on Instruction, 1972-03-1972-04 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Task Force on Innovation in Instruction, 1972-05-1972-06 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Task Force for Innovation on Instruction, 1972-07-1972-10 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Task Force for Innovation on Instruction - Research Files, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Task Force Minutes and Newsletters, 1972-02-1972-10 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Subcommittee Preliminary Recommendations, 1972-05-01 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Preliminary Report - Task Force for Innovation in Instruction, 1972-05 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Subcommittees Reports, 1972-09 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Innovation Instruction - Final Report, 1972-11 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Task Force, 1972-1973 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Task Force, 1973-02-1973-06 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Task Force Recommendations, 1973-1974 (Box 56, Folder 24)
- Series XVI: University Space, 1969-1976
  - Space University, 1969-1971 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - University Space (3 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 57, Folder 2-4)
  - University Space (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 5-6)
  - University Space - Analysis, 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - College of Arts and Sciences - Space (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 8-9)
  - College of Business - Space, 1969-1972 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - College of Engineering - Space, 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - University Space: Cooperative Education, 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - University Space: Telephone Systems, 1971-06-1971-07 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - University Space: Utilization, 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - University Space, 1972-1973 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - University Space: Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1972-1973 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - University Space: Arts and Sciences, 1972-1973 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - University Space: Burruss Auditorium Renovation (2 folders), 1968-1973 (Box 57, Folder 18-19)
  - University Space: Derring, 1972-1973 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - University Space: Engineering, 1971-1973 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - University Space: McBryde, 1971-1973 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - University Space: Patton, 1971-1973 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Space Standards, 1972-1973 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - University Space: Water Resources, 1971-1973 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - University Space, 1973-1974 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Space - Extension, 1973-1974 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Space - Home Economics, 1973-1974 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Space - Veterinary Medicine, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Space - General, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Space - Agriculture, 1974-1975 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Space - Architecture, 1973-1975 (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Space - College of Arts and Sciences (2 folders), 1972-1975 (Box 57, Folder 33-34)
  - Space - College of Business, 1972-1975 (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Space - College of Education, 1973-1975 (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Space - Engineering, 1972-1975 (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - Space - Rental Property, 1974-1975 (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - Space Standards, 1972-1975 (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - Space Needs Assessment and Forecast for the University (SNAFU) (3 folders), 1975 (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
  - Space Needs Assessment and Forecast for the University (SNAFU) Report (2 folders), 1975-12 (Box 58, Folder 3A-3B)
  - Space Needs Assessment and Forecast for the University (SNAFU) Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Series XVII: Summer School and Summer Orientation, 1969-1975
  - Summer Orientation, 1969-1970 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Summer School, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Summer School, 1969-1970 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Summer School Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Orientation, Summer, 1970-1971 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Summer School, 1970-1971 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Summer School, I and II Sessions (2 folders), 1971 (Box 58, Folder 11-12)
  - Summer School Faculty, I and II Summer, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Summer Orientation (4 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 58, Folder 14-17)
  - Summer Orientation Report, 1972-03 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Summer School Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Summer School, I and II Sessions, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Summer Orientation (3 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 58, Folder 21-23)
  - Summer Orientation Review, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Summer School - Comparative Data, 1970-1973 (Box 58, Folder 25-26)
  - Summer School Correspondence, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Summer School Courses (2 folders), 1971-1973 (Box 59, Folder 2-3)
  - Summer School - Education Personnel in Virginia and West Virginia Outreach to Local Businesses, 1971-1973 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Summer School Faculty, I and II Summer Sessions (2 folders), 1973 (Box 59, Folder 5-6)
  - Summer School Flyers, 1971-1974 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Summer School - Intensive Courses (2 folders), 1973 (Box 59, Folder 8-9)
  - Summer School Staff Position Allocations, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Summer Orientation (3 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 11-13)
  - Summer School Courses, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Business - Summer School, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Education, Summer, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Engineering, Summer, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Summer School - Health, Education, and Welfare, 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Summer School Faculty, Sessions I and II (2 folders), 1974 (Box 59, Folder 19-20)
  - Summer Session - Information Requests, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Summer School Plans, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Summer School - Timetable, 1972-1974 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - National Association of Summer Sessions, 1973-1975 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Summer Orientation, 1974-1975 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Summer School, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Summer School - Course Planning, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 27)
- Series XVIII: State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), 1970-1975
  - SCHEV Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - SCHEV Proposed New Degree Programs, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - SCHEV - Research and Development Committee (2 folders), 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 3-4)
  - SCHEV Correspondence (2 folders), 1970-1971 (Box 60, Folder 5-6)